{
    "id": "fa3b353c12f14104914ee18dc6f80ce4",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It was such a comic state of affairs ……………………….. we had to laugh.",
            "description": "The correlative conjunction used in this structure is such...that.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "that",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "42c160ca40434dac9329f58376d17577"
        },
        {
            "question": "The negotiations collapsed …………………………. no agreement could be reached.",
            "description": "All of the above can be used here with slightly different meanings.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "when",
                "since",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "16cce3aeade944fb82ac27ffc541a73a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I like you better …………………………… I like him.",
            "description": "In comparative expressions we use than.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "aa5005bd6e714d529085baddd756627f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will need the car …………………………….. you will have to hire a taxi.",
            "description": "We cannot use then to connect two ideas spoken by the same speaker.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "then",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "93ef130f31514627ab9aa6901a1e7a12"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘I will be busy in the morning’. ‘………………………. I will come in the afternoon.’",
            "description": "Then is used when one speaker replies to another.",
            "answers": [
                "So",
                "Then",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "72de4d2ab0fd42e6a15f538dddfb0237"
        },
        {
            "question": "Many things have happened ………………………….. we last met.",
            "description": "Since can indicate time. It is mainly used with perfect tenses. ",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "since",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0910e70a8e6a459b84a558e58769c72c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Janet can sing beautifully and …………………………… can her sister.",
            "description": "This structure with so is used to add to the sentence before.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "so",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "60debf342ef24d6dba937ea3febee6a2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I scored good marks, …………………………….. I had not prepared for the exam.",
            "description": "Even though has a past reference. It is an emphatic form of though and although.",
            "answers": [
                "even though",
                "even if",
                "even"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f80604ae8ef54804ace31dc4644243b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "She says that she will come …………………………….. there is a bus strike next week.",
            "description": "Even if has a future reference.",
            "answers": [
                "even if",
                "even though",
                "even"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1f31ff5767634a29af806949f2319b53"
        },
        {
            "question": "Grievances cannot be addressed …………………………………. they are spoken about.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "without"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f0745d9fefc94e0cb1691eeeb8c07103"
        },
        {
            "question": "She would rather dance ………………………… sing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c6b79cd01d69411fa392968d1bf4b4af"
        }
    ]
}